The Knicks are back in the finals for
the first time in 27 years.
>> Most of the energy was coming out of my
wallet.
>> I'm outside Madison Square Garden where
tonight's cheapest resale ticket will
cost many fans more than a month's rent
in New York City. Let's find out what
people actually pay. How much did you
spend on the ticket?
>> Ooh, undisclosed. Over 10,000.
>> Around 11,000. 800 each.
>> How much did you pay for the tickets?
>> They're like over 10 grand a seat. The
last time the Knicks played in an NBA
Finals game at Madison Square Garden, it
was 1999. Also against the Spurs. That
year, the Spurs won. Tonight, New York
is spending whatever it takes to rewrite
that ending. Let's go next.
>> So, when did you guys buy the tickets?
>> Today. Couple hours ago.
>> Couple hours ago. I just got off work.
She said we're going.
>> Segeek says the average resale ticket
for tonight's game is $6,500. That's
more than three times the previous
record for any NBA Finals game ever. So,
the thing about New York, we always
going to find a way. Ticket prices go
up. As you can see, we're all outside.
>> Well, you know, we're trying to just see
what we can see. There's some TV's out,
there's phones out. You know, there's a
whole bunch of places to watch the game
and you just feel the excitement in the
city.
>> You can't go anywhere without hearing go
New York, go New York, go. We taking
this home.
>> Four. Nixon 4. Your next and forehead.